<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" lang="en" xml:lang="en">
 <head>
  <title>Fireflix</title>
  <link rel="stylesheet" href="fireflix.css" type="text/css"/>
 </head>
 <body>

  <p>This is a brief overview of things you can do with <a href="http://kin.klever.net/fireflix/">fireflix</a>.</p>
 
  <p>First, you should proceed with authorization. If you haven't done it yet,
  it should happen automatically once you open fireflix sidebar. To clear
  authorization token off of the preferences, right-click on the 'Authorization
  info' part of the sidebar and select 'Sign off' from the pop up menu.</p>

  <h1>In the 'Search' tab</h1>

  <p>Basically, you can search flickr photos here. Either all or yours (keep
  'mine' checked to search your own photos).</p>

  <p>Once you have acquired search results you can browse through them. To open
  any particular picture in a new tab either doubleclick it or hit ENTER.</p>

  <p>While moving through the list of pictures found you should have a little
  preview at the bottom of the window.</p>

  <h1>In the 'Sets' tab</h1>

  <p>This is where you can browse your sets. You can edit some sets properties
  here and, most importantly, you can generate HTML of linked thumbnails for
  sets contents. Use your right mouse button on the photoset.</p>

  <h1>In The 'Uploads' tab</h1>

  <p>To upload pictures you don't even have to select this tab. Drag'n'drop into
  fireflix sidebar should do. There is nothing wrong with going into the tab and
  using 'Add' button either.</p>

  <p>You can add photos to the list, edit their titles and/or tags and once
  you're done with it, trigger upload procedure. Once your images have been
  uploaded, you will be prompted to create a photoset for newly uploaded photos.
  You don't have to, though.</p>

  <h1>Feedback</h1>

  <p>As the extension is at the very early stage of development, feel free to
  provide feedback at <a href="http://kin.klever.net/fireflix/feedback" title="click here to proceed to feedback form">http://kin.klever.net/fireflix/feedback/</a>.</p>

  <div class="copyright">
   <a href="http://www.klever.net/">© Klever Group</a>
  </div>
 </body>
</html>
